[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Clueless, what game do Cher, Tai, Travis and others play at the Val Party with a credit card?", "correct_answer": "Suck and Blow", "incorrect_answers": ["Quarters", "Twister", "Charge it"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Phoenix is the evil side of Marvel Comics character Jean Grey.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In nature, chinchillas can be found in only one color. Which one is it?", "correct_answer": "Grey", "incorrect_answers": ["Black", "Brown", "Beige"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2006 movie starred Jason Statham, Amy Smart and Efren Ramirez.", "correct_answer": "Crank", "incorrect_answers": ["Napoleon Dynamite", "Mirrors", "The Transporter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the softest mineral?", "correct_answer": "Talc", "incorrect_answers": ["Fluorite", "Gypsum", "Calcite"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which old, greedy businessman is ranked #6 on the American Film Institutions list of the top movie villains?", "correct_answer": "Mr. Potter", "incorrect_answers": ["Auric Goldfinger", "Hans Gruber", "Michael Corleone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country does a widow wear purple to mourn her husbands death?", "correct_answer": "Thailand", "incorrect_answers": ["Mexico", "Canada", "United States of America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These substances are added to lotions and creams because they smooth and soften the skin.  There are several hundred different kinds.", "correct_answer": "Emollients", "incorrect_answers": ["Humectants", "Solvents", "Lubricants"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who sang on the first million selling record?", "correct_answer": "Enrico Caruso", "incorrect_answers": ["Thomas Alva Edison", "Louis Armstrong", "Frank Sinatra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actresses co-stars with Alan Rickman in the movie Snow Cake?", "correct_answer": "Sigourney Weaver", "incorrect_answers": ["Emma Watson", "Emma Thompson", "Maggie Smith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The traditional Arab cookies, called Kleicha, are considered the national cookies of this Arab country.", "correct_answer": "Iraq", "incorrect_answers": ["Libya", "Iran", "Lebanon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This agent, present in the skin of grapes, is one of the most important beneficiary agents in wine.  It has antioxidant, anticoagulant, anti-inflammatory and anti-cancer properties.", "correct_answer": "Resveratrol", "incorrect_answers": ["Caffeine", "Flavonoids", "Azulene"]}]